Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Dairy Queen Blizzard flavors,
but lower in calories and higher in
protein. This is the pumpkin pie
blizzard. Let me show you how to make
it. We're starting off with a pumpkin
spice base. So, this involves Fairlife
milk, vanilla bean paste, sweetener,
salt, zantham gum, pumpkin pie spice,
and of course, some fresh canned
pumpkin. Then, you can just blend that
all together using either a hand frother
or even an immersion blender would work
really well for this. Then freeze it for
at least 16 hours. Take it out, run it
under hot water for about a minute, and
then throw it in your creamy on the
light ice cream setting. Once that cycle
is over, you can take it out, scrape
down the sides, and then hollow out a
hole in the center for your mixins. I
use these little mini 100 calorie pie
crust, which are awesome, but feel free
to use any type of pie crust you can
find or even some graham crackers. And
then you can just close that up and
throw it back in your creamy on the
mixing setting, and then you're done.
Also, DQ just dropped a bunch of new
Blizzard flavors, so comment which ones
you want to see next.